Well, the reality today is that agents
are super powerful, but they're
massively unreliable. And this creates
this capability reliability gap. And it
turns out if you have 10 smart things to
say and you say all of them, each of
them will get less attention than if you
said three of them. And this is uh Toby,
founder and CEO of Shopify. And I like
his quotes here. I like the term context
engineering because I think the
fundamental skill of using AI well is to
be able to and this is the key word
state a problem with enough context in
such a way that without any additional
pieces of information the task is
plausibly solvable but one common
pattern is the separation between rules
and knowledge and I'll give an example
from Tessel's content tessle has a spec
registry first of all we define a
knowledge base the second thing we would
do is we will put a little bit of
knowledge or a little bit of rules in
the agents and d file and then down the
rabbit hole it can learn more. So this
is like a human clicking links on a
website and it's very effective. And so
our question was okay we've done this
can we optimize this with context and
we're happy to see that yes yes we can.
Before we jump into this episode I
wanted to let you know that this podcast
is for developers building with AI at
the core. So whether that's exploring
the latest tools, the workflows, or the
best practices, this podcast's for you.
Now, we've had amazing guests like
Olivier Pomel, the CEO of Data Dog,
Matty Stanisowski, the co-founder of 11
Labs, Victor Ripelli, the CEO and
co-founder at Synthesia, and of course,
Tessle's very own Patrick Dwis. And
they're all sharing lessons right from
the frontier of our industry. A really
quick ask, 90% of people who are
listening to this haven't yet
subscribed. So, if this content has
helped you build smarter, hit that
subscribe button and maybe a like. It
really does help us keep bringing the
folks who are actually pushing this
space forward and helping build that AI
native future. All right, back to the
episode.
Now, our next speaker is the uh is the
uh founder and CEO of a little company
called Tessle. Uh 18-month old company.
Um Gipo previously is he's a serial
founder. He he he founded Blaze, which
was acquired. He founded Sneak, a
massively successful developer security
uh company and organization that
actually when we think about it, a lot
of the challenges that that had in and
around moving the the thought process,
moving the moving the mindset of people
to a developer security path is actually
very similar to how we're thinking today
about AI native development. And now
we're going to talk about how AI can be
done collaboratively. So please give it
up for our first keynote speaker,
Gourney.
Hello everyone. Uh, welcome to the first
in person in Native DevCon. Uh, love in
person events, you know, like I think
you you you convey things virtually. I
consume things virtually, but nothing
beats, you know, talking to people and
engaging with them. And I hope you're
all feeling that way. So, thanks for
shipping in, especially in the rain here
in New York. And uh, and I hope you
enjoy the event. and I look forward to
meeting and learning from many of you. I
am Gaparani or Gipo. I am the founder
and CEO of Tessle. Uh and I'm here to
talk about specdriven developments
growth uh from kind of single player to
really how do you use it in a team and
how do you think about ecosystems? Um
let me set the stage first. So hopefully
we're all aligned that AI is
transforming software development. It's
not a little hiccup. It's not a little
change. It's something that is
substantial that is happening. And we've
seen a bunch of evolution already. We've
had two kind of waves of what I think of
as AI augmented software development uh
with the tools that were pioneered by
copilot and cursor that autocomplete
things better. You know that that helped
a lot that build in chat and allow you
to talk to your code and understand
things that cursor pioneered. And then
we uh in this last sort of especially
six months maybe 12, we've seen the rise
of more true AI native which I think of
them as more AI native dev tools because
they're more about delegation. They're
more about ask the agent to do a thing
for you and then interact with it. So
it's a it's a much more substantial
change for us and there's a lot to
learn. And while all of these tools are
are valuable in their own right, they've
all kind of consolidated towards this
agentic behavior. uh and I think it's
pretty clear that that is the future. So
I'll focus on where is that taking us?
You know, how do we make this agentic
development work?
So the reality today is that agents are
are super powerful uh but they're
massively unreliable, right? They're
sort of sometimes spooky, sometimes
kooky. You know, they're they're uh
they're they're amazing and they do
these things that astound you, but then
they just make these foolish mistakes.
Um they're also very untrustworthy.
They'll tell you something is done when
it isn't really. they will break things
along the way as they, you know, you ask
them to build a feature, they'll burn
down the house to to get it done. Uh,
and so they're very powerful, uh, but
they're kind of hard to use. Um, and
this creates this capability reliability
gap, you know, and you see studies like
this one from meter where they they
assess, you know, how how much do
developers think AI tools will make them
better? And you see this is the bar at
the left and people developers, well, I
think it's going to make me faster. I'll
complete something faster and then they
observe how long it actually takes them
to do it and it turns out it actually
was slower. There's a lot of caveats, a
lot of flaws in this study and in any of
the others. It's a very complex area.
But I think everybody relates to the
fact that it's not easy to turn this
power into improved productivity into
something that actually works.
And and so what do we do about it? Well,
what we can't do about it is say, you
know, bury your head in the sand. Like,
let's not use agents is tempting. And,
you know, a good number of people,
probably none in this room are uh are
saying that. Uh but, you know, it's
clearly shortsighted. I mean, this is a
technology that's too powerful that uh
to to kind of ignore or think it would
fade away. It's here. It's going to
shape our development and we need to
think about how do we embrace it, not
how do we ignore it. And so the real
question is how do we help agents? How
do we help agents succeed and close this
capability reliability gap?
Let's look a little bit at a at a
history of attempting to do so. You
know, this is uh our quest for silver
bullets that would make LLMs work uh the
way we want, right? And a bit of a loose
timeline. We start off with, you know,
this is us as the industry thinking
about fine-tuning. Hey, we're going to
tell the LLM here are like tens,
hundreds, maybe thousands of examples of
how I like to code, how you code in my
environment on it, and the LLM's weights
will magically adapt uh and work like
that. And it turns out that this works
very well for brand new skills, for
cases in which you're teaching the LLM
to do something that you didn't know
before. But if it already has opinions,
if it already knows how to code, it's
very hard to sway it. It's kind of like
people, you know, we if if can't teach
an old dog new tricks, right? hard to
sway how someone will behave and so
fine-tuning is useful but it's not a
silver bullet and in fact in many cases
uh it is it is hard to to really have it
shine.
The second kind of wave of technology of
this will solve our problems was was
rag. It's like I will take my prompt and
I will put it into this magical kind of
embedding algorithms and vector
databases will pull out the right
context that I need everything precisely
that I need to know to be able to
address this problem. And again, rag
very powerful when you have your own
keywords and terminology and things like
that. But uh context gathering is more
complicated than that. Uh there's
there's a lot of subtlety often times
things that are not in your prompt.
They're not in that initial path. And so
it remained a useful tool but was deemed
not uh not a silver bullet.
Um the next kind of this will save us
all was the world of big context. You
know what? We don't need to worry about
all this stuff. You know, we've got like
million token, two million token context
windows. will just tell it everything uh
and it will figure it out. It'll just
sort of know what to do. And it turns
out, you know, like I often get uh the
like through my career, I've gotten the
often times the guidance that says if
you have 10 smart things to say and you
say all of them, each of them will get
less attention than if you said three of
them. Uh and and I still struggle to not
say everything I think, but uh it but
it's true. You know, if you say fewer
things, each of them gets more
attention. And NLMs are the same. They
if you if you give it more information
in its context, each of these bits will
get less attention. It would be less
focused and we'll show a little bit of
that in a sec. And so we get into modern
world uh and we have these two
additional tools. One is a gentic
search. You know what? Let's delegate
the actual problem of context creation
to the agent. Let's give it tools to
find the information. That's what we do
as humans. We go, we Google, we look at
files, we uh we do that work. And that
is useful. But again, it's useful when
it's constrained. If you tell someone
just just go find, you know, the
information about anything, it'll take
time to find it. It'll take uh you might
find the wrong information. Uh and, you
know, it's in it's both inefficient and
unbounded and you can get down rabbit
holes that really kind of make things
worse. And so, it's a very very powerful
tool. We'll refer to it back again, but
again, it didn't just solve the problem
because there's another piece that we
need on top of that and that is context
engineering. And that's the sort of the
state of affairs today, which is you
actually have to give up on the magic
solutions and think about what do you
want to tell the agent? What information
does the agent need to succeed? And I
love uh this is uh Toby the uh founder
and CEO of Shopify. It's a very serable
guy, super smart guy, and he was on the
podcast uh uh couple of months ago. And
I like his quotes here which is I like
the term context engineering because I
think the fundamental skill of using AI
well is to be able to and this is the
key word state a problem with enough
context in such a way that without any
additional pieces of information the
task is plausibly solvable. I love that
it's this notion of like let lean into
intelligence but don't assume mind
readading you know like tell it what it
needs to know so that it can succeed.
So context engineering in my mind and I
might be biased is basically the same as
specs. You know this is about we just
had this long conversation about you
know should we call something spec or
context. Uh it doesn't really matter
like for me it is about getting out of
your head and out of your knowledge
getting the the nuggets of knowledge
that you need to uh give the agent to
succeed. And so I'm going to use the
term context and specs interchangeably
throughout this talk. It's the way I see
the world.
So I'm going to go into that sort of
single multi-ecosystem players but
before that I want to remind us that you
can't optimize what you can't measure.
This is a known phrase in the world of
software development but really mostly
you hear it about uh ops because in ops
we are familiar with these systems that
sometimes behave well and sometimes
don't right that the servers sometimes
work sometimes don't sometimes they
crash and so we have to measure them so
we know what's happening so we can
optimize it. Now we have the same
statistical behavior in our development.
You know we have these statistical
creatures agents they build stuff.
Sometimes they work sometimes they
don't. And that means two things. One we
need to leave the notion of agents can
absolutely do this or cannot absolutely
and embrace a statistical number around
their success rate. And two is we have
to measure that. We have to think about
how do we evaluate how do we assess
success and I'll try to give some data
to back some of my statements in this
talk.
So now we'll actually get to the thing
that is on the title which is let's talk
about uh single player. How do you do
context engineering in a single player
context? So um just to demonstrate a
little bit the the base this is a um a
little sample to-do application with a
Jurassic theme that I worked very hard
on uh to just sort of demonstrate it.
And the base context that an agent has
is your project. Here, I'm asking the
agent to add an edit button to each of
the to-do items in my list. And you'll
see the agent automatically go off and
read files in the project. It doesn't
read all of them. It's already doing a
gentic search to load uh some of that
content. Uh and then it would load that
code, understand that code, and uh
sorry, I'll just sort of pause here. Uh
and um uh it it loads that code and
reads that into context. So, I didn't
need to tell it what the to-do item is.
I didn't need to tell it where to put
that button. It had enough information
in the code. And this is the base
context that's important. However,
you'll notice, for instance, that it
created this blue edit button, and that
doesn't fit my beautiful Jurassic theme.
Uh, and it turns out that in the code,
some information is not there. It
doesn't know that I want to stick to my
theme colors. And so, let's tell it to
do that. So we can add explicit context
that doesn't rely on agentic search like
an agent MD file that says always stick
to the theme colors used British
spelling and it will go off and I will
ask the same action you know I will say
add an edit button and it will go off.
it'll do the same type of like dynamic
loading and uh maybe I'll sort of spare
us a moment here uh as we get to the end
you will see that it indeed created uh
the button with my beautiful thing
comments uh and and so this is this is
101 of context engineering at at the
base your project's context your
project's code is the agent's context
how well documented it is whether it is
confusing and has references to old data
structures that you have uh how um uh
reasonable are your file names all of
Those things help the agent load the
right files, but then there's going to
be some information that's not in the
code and you put in your explicit agents
MD, claude MD, cursor rules, local
context. You probably know much of this
already. The challenge is this is nice
when you want to tell it stick to the
theme colors, but typically you have a
lot more to say. There's just a lot that
you want to tell it uh about how to work
in your environment, in your style. And
as we talked about before, if you tell
it's 10 things, it's going to get, you
know, give each of them less attempts
than if you told it three. Uh, and so
this is uh a problem. Before I talk
about how to solve it, let's maybe back
that claim that this is a problem with
some data. So to do that, we took a
little uh game, the team took a little
sort of dodge the blocks game uh that
was vibe coded and asked uh the asked an
agent in this case Cloud Code. Actually
we tried three agents say add a login to
this like add sessionbacked
authentication so this game will be
behind the login. The other thing we did
is we created again with agents uh an
evaluation scorecard like how good is
the security of this thing that you've
just added. This like a benchmark there
are standards today for good rubrics and
then we ran that in three different
modes. One is we ran the agents without
any context and we scored them. The
second is we put into the agents MD or
the equivalent uh the OASP the open web
application security project uh guidance
around authentication about 3 kilobytes
of data and the second is the longer 20
kilobytes of full security guidance that
includes the 3 kilobytes there's no word
that didn't exist in the second one and
indeed as we ran this we saw and I'm
just sort of you know uh this is no
surprise that without any guidance the
agent scored a 65 5% score and with the
guidance with the precise guidance it
got 85% score and if we told it more
things it got a lower score it got 81.
So this was good and it's already
validation we need to know that even
though we expect this behavior now we
have a bit more confidence and there are
many examples of this but also we find
information that is maybe a bit
unexpected. For instance we ran this on
three different agents. We ran it on
claude on codeex and on cursor. And what
you can see is they all fared about the
same mediocre results without any
guidance. There are many pitfalls that
you can have from a security perspective
when you add a login page. But there's a
big difference in how they handle the
deeper context. Claude shined when you
gave it precise instructions, but
dropped a fair bit uh when you gave it
the longer instruction. Codeex didn't do
as well in total, but dealt with the
longer context a lot more. And it's
interesting because it's not obvious to
people that not all agents listen the
same. you we told them the same words.
Some of these actually use the same
model behind them. But agents process
and make many decisions. And you know,
granted, there are 10 runs behind each
of these columns. So maybe there's also
not enough data for statistical
significance, but the results are
substantially different. And you have to
think not just about what is the
question you're asking and the
saturation, but also who are you asking
it.
So, so we have this challenge. We want
to tell agents a lot of things and they
uh you know we can't because it's going
to deteriorate their performance. What
do we do? So it's a broader problem and
there are a lot there's a lot to say
about it. But one common pattern is the
separation between rules and knowledge.
Rules would be a small amount of data
that you're providing it that you're
kind of shoving down their throat.
You're saying this will be in your
agents. You're going to see this every
single time. And they have to be
succinct. And what they should do is
they should include links and references
to guide agentic search around where can
it fetch additional information and that
is the knowledge. And I'll give an
example from Tessle's content. So
hopefully many people on this uh uh in
this event uh here or virtually know
that Tesla has a spec registry and we
it's a uh a dependency system for
knowledge. You can publish context into
it in this form we call tiles and then
you can consume that down to your uh to
your consumers right to your agents uh
and it will adapt it to the local agent
and you can do it for your context but
we also pre-populated the registry with
over 10,000 specs or context uh that uh
that that helps agents use open source
libraries better. We've analyzed those
libraries, we've iterated, we've
evaluated and we created those. So let's
let's look a little bit at what is the
structure of those. Um in first of all
we define a knowledge base. So well what
is the knowledge that you want? So you
do that in this tessle.json file in our
example. There are variations of it.
We'll touch uh to say this is the
information I want. In this case I have
a bunch of libraries. I want to know how
to use them. And then you'll see that
each one of those is fragmented into
pieces. So the agent doesn't need to
suck it all up right away. especially
for some of these libraries, there's a
lot to say. You don't want to hog the
context window. So, there's a bunch of
different files.
The second thing we would do is we will
put a little bit of knowledge or a
little bit of rules in the agents MD
file and we'll say here's a link to your
knowledge. Uh we actually it's a bit
longer over here, but we also give a
little bit of instruction of uh what is
the structure of the knowledge you might
find to the agent, but it's a very small
amount of context that is in the rules
and always loaded. And then if you click
that knowledge MD file, you will get a
markdown file that the agent can easily
find out which libraries do you have a
little bit of information about them and
where can it learn more and then down
the rabbit hole it can learn more. It
has an index file it explains about in
this case Nex.js and then it can in that
file find links to additional
information. So this is like a human
clicking links on a website right you
have a summary thing you're expanding a
section or you're clicking through and
it's very effective. This is a good way
to give the agent uh uh a way to find
the right information. Lean into its
agentic search capabilities, but don't
ask it to sort of browse the web and
just figure it out.
So hopefully at this point you're
saying, well, show me some data. I
realized as I was building it that this
is a Jerry Maguire reference and not
everybody knows that. It might be like a
my age is starting to defer of it. Like
it does say show me the money typically.
Um so okay can we see some data right I
make this claim that this is a good way
and a good effective way to to make the
agents work. Let's see some data. I'll
show two examples of this. First is uh
thanks to the great work that uh the
team at Versel has done on Nex.js. So
Nex.js JS is a very well uh wellused
very popular JavaScript framework that
is maintained and built today by the
Verscell team and they published as a
thought leader in the AI space uh a
benchmark about that tries to measure
how well can agents use Nex.js and they
created about 50 different test cases uh
and uh they ran it through different
agents to see how well they can address
those. It's interesting by the way
immediately to see that even though
Nex.js is so popular and has so much
content, it's like the sweetheart of the
training data, right? It's well
documented. It's an amazingly like clear
set of data. The top agents, the ones
that did the best, still only got a 42%
score in this benchmark. And so that's
already interesting and a bit sobering,
but it goes to show, okay, can we
improve this with context engineering?
and in general that if you measure this
now I bet you all the agents are now
working on optimizing it and so our
question was okay we've done this can we
optimize this with context can we test
our uh uh our our knowledge like these
tiles that we create do they actually
make it better and we ran this eval
because we already had the eval so we
just had to compare the two test cases
and we're happy to see that yes yes yes
we can with the knowledge the success
rate like for us it was about 40% % in
our uh uh test environment. Success rate
of using SJS on this benchmark, it
jumped up to 92% if we got that info.
This is if we got you know the very
thoroughly created piece of information.
But we also find for instance that a
smaller prompt midway that just guides
the agent to look at the things that you
care about uh in this case some linting
and some build errors actually also
bumped up the process substantially. So
sometimes it's knowledge and sometimes
it's steering around what is it to pay
attention to.
This is great for next.js but this was a
very thorough benchmark set that
required a lot of attention. We can't do
that for everything. But what you can do
when you evaluate your content and you
have something that is uh you don't have
the sort of the bandwidth to create a
deep benchmark for is that you can use
LLMs to create evaluation data. And so
we took 270 random libraries and we
asked the LLM to create test exercises
for them, a scorecard to evaluate how
well they did on that test and then we
ran it through agents. The data I have
here is for claude code. We saw similar
data for cursor and then eventually you
ask an LLM to judge the result with that
rubric. And indeed when we ran that we
saw that on average across those 270 we
bumped up the success rate from about
60% to about 81% uh in open source in
agents ability to consume open source
across these 270 libraries and we did
that with a little bit of a shortening
of the time. So the agents were a lot
more successful in a little bit less
time a little bit faster which was
really encouraging. So this was great
and this is again the validation part.
We also had you always find these bits
of information that you don't know how
to expect. uh some interesting
information about the age of a library.
And so this graph shows with the same
test the success rate of the agent. This
is cloud code across uh uh correlated to
the uh age of the libraries. The
libraries at the left are the oldest.
The libraries on the right are the
newest that this is release date just as
a simple measure. And it's interesting
to see how the libraries that are 5 to
10 years old, those are the ones that
the agents do the best with. And we've
seen this with other agents as well. Uh,
and the distance is substantial. And
that makes sense because very old
libraries, they might have they might
have confusing information on the web.
Uh, maybe they don't have as much web
representation if they're truly old. And
the very new libraries, often times they
haven't accumulated enough information
on the web. And some of their data is
actually after the training data. And
our theory was that with uh with the
tiles, we actually can flatten that
line, right? We because we gave them the
information, they have it, so they
should use it. And indeed, we've seen
that we elevate the result more broadly.
And this was useful because it matches
our kind of anecdotal experience that um
using this type of knowledge, using the
right context, sometimes just helps and
sometimes it turns it from it doesn't
work to it works.
Um I'll move on to multiplayer, but just
one thing to say is that in context
engineering is actually a lot more than
what I'm showing right now. And there
are many many different tools and one
notable one is the ability to use a sub
agent in claude and now a few other
agents to be able to give it its context
and focus it. So there's a lot more to
do here and it's a worthy domain to
invest in.
So with that let's talk from single
player talk about multiplayer. In
multiplayer the question is in your team
in your organization what context do you
want to provide and when? What are the
ways in which you can share context
across the team? I'll talk about three
versions of this. The first and kind of
easiest most sort of uh direct way to
share context is to put stuff in the
repo. As we said, the project itself is
the base context for an agent. And so if
you check in an agent MD file, anybody
that uses that repository would load it.
It's the repo or the path within the
repo. This is great and you should do it
and it is a perfect fit for things that
are reposification
about how this application behaves or
things like that. Awesome. Perfect place
to do it. Highly recommended. Uh where
it slightly falters is uh one is cross
repository information. Your best
practices, shared libraries and all
those feels a bit odd to check those
into a repository. Would you check them
into multiple repositories? You might
run a different solution. And the second
is uh and I'm picking a little bit on
backlog MD over here. You know it's a
great framework. We had a great workshop
yesterday about it. Um and you can see
though that you know those who adopt
agents and lean into them. What you find
in the repos is you find many duplicate
files. You find your sort of Gemini MD
and cloud MD and agent MD and cursor
rules and you'll find skills. You'll
find GitHub stuff and and that's not
awesome. Uh and it's not that you have
this many files that is the problem, but
rather that they are duplicative.
there's often content that is very
similar within each one of them. So
that's a challenge.
The second tool that you have to
accumulate and to provide shared context
makes to your team is to give agents
tools to gather context. Uh most common
is of course browsing the web but also
things that are more focused like hey
use this to uh uh this MCP tool to be
able to go and fetch uh code from GitHub
repositories and load them. So this is
I'd say you know first of all super
useful for discovery and exploration
like know you you don't know which
library you're going to use clearly you
don't have the context for that library
as you're exploring you should have
dynamic tools to go and fetch that. It's
also great for dynamic data like uh uh
production data about how your system
ran or you know something that is
constantly changing. So for those it is
amazing. Uh it is not great when there's
a high potential to get the wrong
answer. Versioning is a is a strong
example of that. And if you're using a
version that's not the latest and your
agent wants the latest GitHub repo, it's
going to get the wrong information to
operate with. And for complex topics
where there's subtleties, you know,
authentication related topics or um just
sort of complex environments,
it's also highly inefficient for
repeatedly needed info. So let's say you
can go off and find the relevant commit
at the relevant repo and read the code.
If you need this information seven times
a day, you know, 5 days a week, why like
why wouldn't you sort of gather that
context one time, store it, evaluate it
and then optimize for that? Which gets
me to the third mode which is today kind
of the cutting edge and it's the notion
of curated context or curated knowledge.
What you would have seen is over the
last couple of months you've seen a lot
of progress from all the big agents uh
uh providing reusable context
frameworks. So they have you has you saw
cloud skills you saw cursor team rules
you saw GitHub copilot spaces uh and you
know these are these are kind of
acknowledgements from these agent
companies to say well we don't want the
agent to reinvent it every time we
actually want to allow you to share
things and to share practices and that's
great I highly recommend these platforms
you should learn about your environment
for it they're great for cross
repository knowledge uh they're great
when you're using often times you start
seeing people use uh maybe like a you
have a security code view bot that runs
in your review surrounding, but that
same context. You also want it when
you're building locally and maybe when
you're assessing an incident with
another agent. So, it's great to have
not just crossdevelopment repo, but also
cross use case knowledge. Uh, and
because they're built natively, they
tend to be kind of nice and elegant in
terms of how they interact, you know,
clawed with its skills, cursor with its
roles, etc. Uh, they're a bit of an
overkill for single repo information.
Maybe that's not too bad. But really the
biggest challenge with them is that they
are single agent. Um, and that kind of
begs the question of do we think long
term that knowledge and context should
be managed per agent, right? Do you
think in your organization, in your
practice, do you expect that you would
use one agent for your org over time?
And I think the answer to that is no.
Like I think just like any technologies,
technologies will be better at one thing
versus the other. They will move. they
will change. Companies are big, people
will have preferences
and that knowledge as a whole should be
something that is a core competency of
the knowledge that you have and it
should be adapted per agent but it
should be your asset that is broader. So
that's the approach we have at Tessle.
You've sort of seen a bit of this
already. We have the Tesl JSON and when
you install this knowledge then it will
it will adapt it to the relevant agent.
It will store it as a cursor role or it
would store it as a as an agent MD or
whatever that is. Uh and then also once
we download that knowledge, the
knowledge is there as files and so you
can use it in whatever way that you
want. We do provide tools to make it
easier and better to work with it. We
want it to be seamless, but you're not
locked in to you need to use those tools
if you want to use different tools to
consume it. So we think this is
important when we think about uh uh kind
of broader long-term context management
and development.
And in fact, we're doubling down on
this. And just as a slight plug here,
you know, we are expanding the registry
into a full-blown TESL uh agent
enablement platform uh that will help
you gather and and this type of
knowledge like the packages you've seen,
create and run evaluations for them,
distribute them so that every repository
gets its knowledge uh and then help you
optimize that over time. Uh so this is a
commercial product and if you're
interested in being uh being part of it,
uh come come talk to us, see us or email
us at contactes.io. fail if you're
online.
So that's a good segue for just the
closing points around ecosystem context.
And you know when I just sort of sang
the sort of the uh the praises of why
ecosystemwide context from the registry
is helpful and you should use it and
it'll help you today. But in the long
run you do have to wonder who should
create this type of open source context.
you know, we we come along to someone
else's library and we create these agent
docs for them and we track them and that
you know we do it today because it's
helpful today and we want to help but
long-term is that right and I think the
answer is no like I think over time kind
of open source context is really an
aspect of agent experience and it is the
creator's responsibility if you are an
open source maintainer if you are a
vendor it's your responsibility to have
a great developer experience it's also
your experience your responsibility to
have a great agent experience. You know,
it is it is in your control. It is
something that you can choose where to
invest and context is your best tool for
that. Context is both your documentation
and your UX. You know, you need to think
about what is it that you say there. How
do you distribute that to your users?
You know, do you want this indeed to be
single agent or multi- aent? And eval
are your tests. They're your moment of
defining what is correct and what is not
correct. And so, you should invest in
those. You should define them. And you
should ask your users for feedback on
when they work and when they don't work.
And you're it's your responsibility, but
you're not alone. You know, you have
asked to help with our technology with
our platform on it. You know, feel free
to talk to us. You have the amazing AI
native dev uh community that you should
tap and they will help you. And
together, I think we want to create this
successful methodologies and actual
context that will help us all consume
software together better. Uh, and if we
achieve all of that, then we'll help
we'll successfully put everything in the
right contest. Thank you.